Peter Riggs

Denver, CO (731) 661-1525 Peter92riggs@gmail.com

SKILLS

Motivated hard worker with a strong background in customer service and hospitality. Has been promoted at every job held and entrusted with important tasks and responsibilities such as safe combinations, security codes, and floor supervision. Has years of experience in the Theater, and has strong presentation skills. Completed University of Denver's Coding Boot Camp in may 2022 and has experience in HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, Express.js, React.js, Node.js, progressive web apps, agile methodology, computer science, database theory, MongoDB, MySQL, Git, and several others.

EMPLOYMENT EXPERIENCE

Thunderbolt LLC, Denver CO - Carpenter, Site Supervisor.

September 2019 - September 2021

- Experience reading and implementing architectural designs.
- Fielded inspections.
- Supervised site and managed subcontractors.

Bar Pastoral, Chicago IL - Assistant Manager and Bartender

August 2016 - August 2019

- Moved up in the company from Server Assistant to Server and then to Assistant Manager and part time Bartender
- Trained new hires in hospitality procedures.
- Managed the entire restaurant floor and bar three days a week.
- Oversaw opening and closing procedures, including safe access and security codes.
- Gained considerable knowledge of eclectic wines and artisan cheeses.

Leaders Credit Union, Jackson TN - Teller

July 2014 - June 2016

- Began as a part time Teller Assistant and was promoted to a full time Teller position.
- Executed customer transactions, including deposits, withdrawals, money orders and checks.
- Managed a wide variety of customer service and administrative tasks to resolve customer issues quickly and efficiently.

• Ensured superior customer experience by addressing customer concerns, demonstrating empathy and resolving problems on the spot.

EDUCATION

Union University, Jackson TN - Bachelor of Arts, Philosophy

August 2010 - May 2014

Developed the skills of diligent studying, critical thinking, attention to detail, and interpersonal communication.

University of Denver, Denver CO - Certificate, Web Development.

January 2022 - May 2022

Attended University of Denver's Coding Boot Camp.